Resume



Basic Info.

Name: JackyWu Gender: Male

Date of Birth: 1982/4/14 Residency: Shanghai-Minhang
Yrs. of Experience: > 10 years Email: ecstorm@gmail.com

Mobile Phone: 15021843860

Home Tel: 086-021-33887095 Current Salary: 150,000-300,000RMB

Hukou: Shanghai
Height: 170cm
Marital Status: Married
Political Status: Citizen

Address: #171, NO 699, Lianqing Road Minhang District, Shnanghai China

Postal Code: 201100

Website: http://www.jacky-wu.com

QQ: 38206377

Self Assessment

I think I am a smart person. Funny, easy going, open minded. I am good at PHP, Rails, Django (Python) base on Linux or FreeBSD. Familiar with Java and Linux system management. Like open source and working on Linux platform. Working with database like MySQL and MongoDB. About 8 yrs work experience. For the managing section, I have about 2 year experience for leading a 5 people small team.

Career Objective

I can start: within 1 month
Type of Employment: Full-time

Desired Industry: Computers, Software; Internet/E-commerce; Banking; Automobile & Components;

Education/Training/Universities and Colleges

Desired Location: Shanghai

Desired Salary: 20,000-29,999/Month

Desired Position: Computer, Software; Internet/E-Commerce/Online Game; IT-Management

Work Experience

2013/5--Present: Moca Shanghai Tech Co, ltd. (150-500 people)

Industry: Advertising

IT Senior Software Engineer

Develop & Maintain mobile advertising network. Android Development.

2010/7--2012/8:Moker Corp(

Industry: Internet/E-commerce

IT Department

Technical Director/Manager

Manage a small team. Work on maintaining and developing Websites, desktop Applications. Try to pick the suitable technologies and making rules for the technical team to make sure our code to be extendable and strong. We use Php & Mysql to develop the website adn base on Nginx +php-Fpm web server. And Adobe Air to develop the desktop application called Digital book reader.

2009/5--2010/6: The United Road (500-1000 people)

Industry: Transportation/Logistic/Distribution

IT Senior Software Engineer

Building Quote Application about vehicle transportation. Actually it is a online OA system. Including CRM, Quote system, Office management. Using php and Ms SQL running under Apache server.

2008/6--2009/4:Daibiao(Shanghai) Co, 1td. (

Industry: Computers, Software

IT Senior Software Engineer

develop and maintein travel website and Music SNS website. using php, mysql, Linux etc. The travel website is called yiqilai.com. (It is quit now) Base on a wiki system writtenby C. And other sub system is written by php On centos. The Music SNS website is full written by PHP. Mysql is as a database. And the web server is Apache on Centos. Use Memcached to solve the high currence problem of Mysql This company close down in 2009.

2007/8--2008/5:Spill group Asia(50-150 people)

Industry: Computers, Software

Tec Software Engineer

Develope and maintain www.game.com.cn, danji.game.com.cn, www.xiaoyouxi.com website, including the database design. use php, mysql, ajax and so on. This is a flash game website. Use LVS to implement the web server load balance. And shell script to synchronize between each server.

2005/8--2007/8:AsiaLab(

Industry: Internet/E-commerce

IT Internet/E-Commerce Software Engineer

Work for outsource. Developed some website. By using PHP, Java, Flash www.torreschina.com.cn www.eyebuydirect.com www.88brands.com www.primulaproducts.com www.hyperprousa.com

 $2004/7 -\!-2005/7 \colon\! \text{Companyon.com} \, (50 -\!150 \text{ people})$

Industry: Internet/E-commerce

IT Internet/E-Commerce Software Engineer

Develop website for clients. By using PHP , ASP

2003/7 - 2004/7: Cityyouth.cn(

Industry: Internet/E-commerce

IT Internet/E-Commerce Software Engineer

develop www.cityyouth.cn

Project Experience

2010/7 -- 2012/8 : Bookteller.com
Software Environment: Windows+Centos

Hardware Environment: PC

Development Tools: Eclipse+PHP & Flexbuilder

Project Description: bookteller.com, bookteller.com.tw, these website provide reading picture book and animation

books. Using PHP with ZendFramework and Mysql And a Reader, written by Adobe Air , which can

read these books on client's machine.

Responsibility: Manage a small to develop the website and Reader. Including requirement, code design, code

review, coding work.

2009/5 -- 2010/6 : QMS Software Environment: Windows

Hardware Environment: PC

Development Tools: Eclipse+php

Project Description: online vehicle transport quote system.

Responsibility: Database design , Code design and program coding

2008/6 -- 2009/4 : Daibiao SNS website

Software Environment: CentOS Hardware Environment: PC Development Tools: Gedit

Project Description: www.daibiao.com SNS website focus on Music and American culture ,most of Streat Culture

www.yiqilai.com.cn , tourist wiki website

Responsibility: Database design , Code design and program coding

2007/8 -- 2008/5 : game.com.cn Software Environment: Windows Hardware Environment: PC

Development Tools: Eclipse+php Plugin

Project Description: website for flash online game We develop a new version for this site. Use php, Mysql On linux

server.

Responsibility: Program develop

2005/8 -- 2007/7 : E-commerce
Software Environment: Windows
Hardware Environment: PC

Development Tools: Eclipse+php

Project Description: torreschina.com.cn www.eyebuydirect.com www.88brands.com and so on

Responsibility: base on oscommerce

2004/6 -- 2005/8 : OA (Office Automatization)

Software Environment: Windows Hardware Environment: PC

Development Tools: Eclipse+SSH

Project Description: OA (Office Automatization), EMAIL system, calendar, note book, address book, personnel

management, financial control

Responsibility: some modules design and develop

Education

2000/9 -- 2003/7 Shanghai Second Polytechnic Computer Networking Associate

University

courses: data Construction, Operating system, VB, Java, C++, autocad, Software engineering

Training

2002/11 -- 2003/3 Shanghai Eroad Education SCJP

certificate from SUN

Language Skills

English (Excellent): Listening & Speaking (Good), Reading & Writing (Good)

IT Skills

Skill Name Skill Level Experience JavaScript Expert 48Month JSP Advanced 12Month PHP Expert 60Month **PERL** 12Month Basic E-Commerce 36Month Expert SQL Server 36Month Expert Java Expert 48Month 48Month Linux Expert

Miscellaneous Info.

Objective: I like technology, like to spend much time to learn new skills. Most of projects I worked

are all B/S. I like open source. I like to work with different tools and programming language, such as php, java, Rails, Python. Focus on web server load balance. And database cache server, like memcached and Tokyo Tyrant. And high performance, high concurrence mysql server. Recently, I am styding the source code of Tornado. My avocation is something like

reading, sports, cooking. I love technique.

Evaluation Report



MAST Report